

www.nunogois.comlinkedin.com/in/nuno-goisgithub.com/nunogois

@ me@nunogois.com✔ @nunogois_dev✔ Torres Vedras, Portugal

About Me

Driven 31 years old Full-Stack Developer from Portugal with over 10 years of professional experience. Passionate for the job, love putting skills to the test, facing challenges in a creative and perfectionist way. Experienced with every step of developing and delivering cross-platform, modern and responsive software. Worked with several different technologies across the stack, always willing to learn more and improve skills. Biggest strengths lie in bringing a focused, creative and out-of-the-box approach to challenges, leveraging hard-working and quick learning traits.



Tech stack includes, but is not limited to:

JavaScript, TypeScript, Vue, Quasar, Nuxt.js, Jest, React, React Native, Next.js, Expo, Svelte, Socket.io, .NET, C#, Python, Go, Java, C, C++, SQL Server, MySQL, SQLite, MongoDB, Redis, GraphQL, Apollo GraphQL, Contentful, Elasticsearch, Node.js, Express, ESLint, Prettier, Webpack, jQuery, Tailwind CSS, Bulma, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, Sass, Stylus, Git, GitHub, GitLab, Markdown, Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, Cloudflare, AWS, Google Cloud, Oracle Cloud, Firebase, Docker, Jenkins, Trello, Slack, Discord, Photoshop, PowerShell, Android, Windows, macOS, Linux, Pop!_OS

Work Experience

Zoi

06/2021 - Current

Full-Stack Developer assigned to Digital Innovations.

Worked close to partners as a developer in exploratory projects using innovative cloud solutions.

Contributed to a React Native app project by developing features and fixes for the app.

Developed a mock package used internally for testing and debugging purposes.

Followed best-practices and guidelines, including writing Unit and E2E tests.

Worked on a dynamic multicultural team that follows an Agile / Scrum methodology.

Shared knowledge and learned with teammates through pair programming.

IQA - Sistemas de Gestão da Qualidade

03/2011 - 05/2021

Full-Stack Developer of multiple projects using many different technologies.

Developed AGIR ®, a Quality Management Software (QMS), Process Management (BPM) and Document control software. Worked on the platform since 2011: From ASP.NET, SQL Server, Web API, .NET WinForms or Java to Windows Services and Office Add-Ins, (...).

One of the main features of the platform is its flexibility - features like an intuitive Form Designer, a custom JavaScript framework and a business logic assistant mean that it is able to do adapt to every customer need.

Worked close to the project manager and customers to ensure that every product meets requirements in a versatile, modern and performant way. Helped the customer on every step when needed - Configuration, deployment, troubleshooting, etc.

Developed and provided APIs, tools and other custom mechanisms in order to adapt and integrate with existing solutions and products.

Developed a solid foundation for the company's next project, Wisibi, using Quasar Framework (Vue.js) and .NET Core Web API, following all the best practices.

Helped setup and manage the team's Trello, TFS, GitHub, Jenkins and other services.

Shared knowledge with teammates through training.

Education

Escola Superior de Tecnologia de Setúbal Instituto Politécnico de Setúbal

Degree in Computer Engineering (Unfinished) 2007 - 2010

Escola Secundária Madeira Torres

Computer Technology Professional Course 2004 - 2007

Thank you for your time.
Feel free to browse my website or contact me for further information.

Please notice that this version may not be up to date.
In case of doubts, refer to the live version:
cv.nunogois.com